<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Blockchain & Crypto Economics]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Blockchain & Crypto Economics]]></description>
        <link>http://crypto.think-like.me/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2017 20:53:40 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="http://crypto.think-like.me/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2017 20:53:38 GMT</pubDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What is Blockchain?]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1><strong>What is Blockchain?</strong></h1>,<p>Bitcoin is being touted as a possible new economic foundation, but what is actually making Bitcoin and other crypto currencies work? You might have heard about something called the blockchain. To cut it short a blockchain is a public ledger distributed across a decentralized network of computers.</p>,<p>In this post I have tried to collect a number of useful whitepapers, articles and blogs explaining the Blockchain concept. I hope you will find it useful and learn a thing or two about blockchain technology</p>,<p>The article below from CoinDesk is a good guide for people who wants to know more about bitcoin and blockchain. In the end of this article CoinDesk have provided a number of very useful links for diving deeper into the crypto world.</p>,<p><a href="https://www.coindesk.com/information/what-is-blockchain-technology/" title="Click to read full article">Click to read full article..</a></p>]]></description>
            <link>http://crypto.think-like.me/beginners-guide-to-bitcoin/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">18a37c89-a473-405c-918f-7b85eb564f47</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 15:43:15 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ethereum - The machinery of change - Stork and Crow BV - Medium]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Ethereum - The machinery of change - Stork and Crow BV - Medium</h1><p>You wake up, and see that $17.27 was automatically deducted from your primary wallet, as you had authorized to happen every day, to pay the rent for your apartment.</p><img src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/2000/0*0GIMZbPL3szzmKRm.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://medium.com/@jpa_of_snc/ethereum-the-machinery-of-change-60de08222480</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">8ef0df26-fa5e-4540-af95-e2ccfeaf1d13</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2017 00:25:03 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[I Looked Into SegWit, and Here's What I Saw - Steemit]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>I Looked Into SegWit, and Here&apos;s What I Saw - Steemit</h1><p>In light of the upcoming Bitcoin fork, I finally decided to look into exactly what Segwit is, and form my opinions based on the technical and economic realities, rather than opinions and impressions I&apos;ve found online. In this post, I will share what I learned.</p><img src="https://steemitimages.com/DQmZPuWgWLogGPZNdtKsnUfdANvhACWXQeR4AswjqfrnTr6/truck.jpeg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://steemit.com/bitcoin/@modprobe/i-looked-into-segwit-and-here-s-what-i-saw</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">9979c3d1-20f7-456d-b044-94947eb52261</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2017 02:52:48 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Motherboard Bitcoin and Ethereum Primer]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><img src="https://imgflo.herokuapp.com/graph/2b2431f8e7ba7b0/696b495d9eac72b23497909b0ead6899/croprotate.jpeg?cropheight=675&cropwidth=892&degrees=0&input=https%3A%2F%2Fvideo-images.vice.com%2Farticles%2F59431309df10a05676b8f847%2Flede%2F1497612065665-shutterstock_653153323.jpeg%3Fcrop%3D1xw%3A0.8364312267657993xh%3Bcenter%2Ccenter%26resize%3D1200%3A%2A&x=149&y=0"><h1>The Motherboard Bitcoin and Ethereum Primer</h1><p>Your entry portal to the world of cryptocurrency.</p></article>,<p>2017.06.16</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://crypto.think-like.me/the-motherboard-bitcoin-and-ethereum-primer/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">bb8b5a5f-b76b-4c2b-872f-82da452babde</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2017 04:23:45 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Bitcoin's Blockchain Could Power an Alternate Internet]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>2015.01.13</p>,<article><img src="https://imgflo.herokuapp.com/graph/2b2431f8e7ba7b0/c15c5be1a052a3e98dc41505300f330f/noop.jpeg?input=https%3A%2F%2Fcdn-images-1.medium.com%2Fmax%2F1200%2F1*Ck3cQIL3-nAmpPpCdGIuBg.jpeg"><h1>How Bitcoin&apos;s Blockchain Could Power an Alternate Internet</h1><p>There&apos;s this hopelessly geeky new technology. It&apos;s too hard to understand and use. How could it ever break the mass market? Yet developers are excited, venture capital is pouring in, and industry players are taking note. Something big might be happening. That is exactly how the Web looked back in 1994&hairsp;-&hairsp;right before it exploded.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://backchannel.com/how-bitcoins-blockchain-could-power-an-alternate-internet-bb501855af67</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">48c7adf2-8266-4dac-b43e-52c5c2685c14</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 17:04:53 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Have Fun by Mining Ether with AWS Spot - James Wiggins - Medium]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Have Fun by Mining Ether with AWS Spot - James Wiggins - Medium</h1><p>A CloudFormation template that deploys an elastic Spot Fleet on AWS to mine Ether. Note: Based on some comments from this article I want to be clear: this article is not investment advice.</p><img src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1200/1*y-B9LaFU2d7L8c4qeTVDMA.png"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://medium.com/@james.s.wiggins/get-rich-quick-by-mining-ether-with-aws-spot-c7b7a3bdc149</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">beb2d426-0518-4c12-8433-72572e0497e6</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 17:36:14 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Blockchain Show]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Podcast about blockchain and crypto currencies. I find The Blockchain Show very informative as they touch on various aspects of the blockchain and crypto economy. I’ve learned about new technologies, interesting startups and new projects being build on the blockchain. I highly recommend subscribing to this podcast to get the latest news about</p>,<article><img src="https://imgflo.herokuapp.com/graph/2b2431f8e7ba7b0/9159d0c2a835f73baab89d7ccf459259/noop.jpg?input=http%3A%2F%2Fstatic.libsyn.com%2Fp%2Fassets%2F3%2F3%2F3%2F7%2F33374076d17e6977%2Fheight_250_width_250_NewTBCSlogo2017.jpg"><h1>The Blockchain Show</h1><p>The Blockchain Show with Steve Anderson, Sarah Hempfling, and Ethan Kinderknecht. The Blockchain Show is a podcast that demystifies and promotes widespread adoption of cryptocurrencies and distributed ledger technology.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://crypto.think-like.me/the-blockchain-show/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">986ad3b0-0ec1-4702-915a-a09a66cd71e3</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2017 15:08:03 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A beginner's guide to Tezos - Linda Xie - Medium]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>A beginner&apos;s guide to Tezos - Linda Xie - Medium</h1><p>According to the Tezos (&quot;Tay-zos&quot;) website, &quot;Tezos is a new decentralized blockchain that governs itself by establishing a true digital commonwealth.&quot; A commonwealth is a group that chooses to be linked together because of their shared goals and interests. Tezos aims to have their token holders make decisions together to govern the platform and improve it over time.</p><img src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1600/1*cLjDJYqI1_3cOMPmVCLIAw.png"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://medium.com/@linda.xie/a-beginners-guide-to-tezos-c9618240183f</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">a6a97eca-be97-4070-9204-1bf6627867bb</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 18:07:26 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Traders Plan for Correction as Cryptocurrency Market Tops $100 Billion - CoinDesk]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Traders Plan for Correction as Cryptocurrency Market Tops $100 Billion - CoinDesk</h1><p>The total value of all publicly traded cryptocurrencies may be at an all-time high, but trader confidence isn&apos;t keeping pace. After rising more than 1,500% from just over $7bn on 1st January, the market is beginning to show signs that its rapid ascent in 2017 may be slowing.</p><img src="https://media.coindesk.com/uploads/2017/06/shutterstock_637929982.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.coindesk.com/traders-plan-correction-cryptocurrency-market-tops-100-billion/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">78ada50e-3712-46ec-b718-76da52593479</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 15:33:56 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Binance Trading View (Basic) - Beginners Guide]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>Binance Trading View (Basic) - Beginners Guide</h1>,<p>In this post I will try to give a quick and easy overview of the different elements you will see when you go to the basic Trading View on Binance. In another post I will explain the Advanced Trading View.</p>,<p>I will try to give a short explanation for each of the elements below the picture.</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/e54fe97e-9de1-4717-9c0e-ee2a1a4f00b3.png" alt="In this post I will try to give a quick and easy overview of the different elements you will see when you go to the basic Trading View on Binance.">,<ol><li>1. You have the option to trade pairs with BTC, ETH, BNB or USDT. USDT is capped to the US $, so they theoretically should have the same value at any given time. This you can use to get an indication on how much your investment is worth at any given moment.</li><li>Once you’ve selected your main coin in step 1 (BTC, ETH, BNB or USDT), you will now be able to select a coin you want to trade your main coin against. In the example you will see that BTC is selected as the main pair, and ADA/BTC is the pair selected.</li><li>Last price is the last traded price. You will eventually see that this matches the last trade in the Trade history (see #9). Since BTC is selected, it is the last price in BTC, it is 0.00002604 satoshi per ADA coin. This is equivalent to approximately $0.48 at the time of this writing.</li><li>Shows you how much the value of ADA has changed in relation to BTC over the past 24 hours. In this example ADA has gained 24% against BTC. This means that if you bad bought ADA for 1BTC 24 hours ago, you would now have 1.24BTC if you sold all your ADA.</li><li>24h High indicates what the highest price has been within the last 24 hours. This can help you get an idea about where the price is exactly when you look at the chart. In this case, it is in fact quite a bit below the highest point within the last 24 hours (1-(0.00002604/0.00003090)= -15.73%).</li><li>24h Low indicates the lowest price the coin has had past 24 hours.</li><li>24h Volume is the total volume that has been traded for this pair. In this case a total worth of 9,764.35402074 BTC has been traded with ADA coin.</li><li>This is the orderbook, and this is where you will see all existing open orders. The ones in red are the open sell orders and the ones below in green are the existing open buy orders. An open sell order means that someone has put their ADA up for sell at a certain price. In this example you will see that the lowest price someone currently are willing to sell ADA for is 0.00002605, while the highest price anyone is willing to pay is 0.00002604. This is also known as the spread. This can be a good indicator for you to see if there is a lot of support for the coin, in case the price drops. This can however be a very tricky indicator because there are so many bot traders, which have algorithms setup to dynamically open and close their buy/sell orders when the market moves. Thus, never solely rely on this when you evaluate whether or not the market is ripe for you to buy/sell. Use it in combination with your regular analysis and long term plan.</li><li>Is the trading history, which shows you the previous orders for ADA/BTC in this example. As you will see the last traded price was 0.00002604, which matches the Last Price up in the left upper corner.</li></ol>]]></description>
            <link>http://crypto.think-like.me/binance-trading-view-basic-beginners-guide/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">18cb3ab0-891e-46ad-b6c6-569dc21e9832</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 12:40:55 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>