<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Blockchain & Crypto Economics]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Blockchain & Crypto Economics]]></description>
        <link>http://crypto.think-like.me/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2017 05:29:31 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="http://crypto.think-like.me/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2017 05:29:30 GMT</pubDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What is Blockchain?]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1><strong>What is Blockchain?</strong></h1>,<p>Bitcoin is being touted as a possible new economic foundation, but what is actually making Bitcoin and other crypto currencies work? You might have heard about something called the blockchain. To cut it short a blockchain is a public ledger distributed across a decentralized network of computers.</p>,<p>In this post I have tried to collect a number of useful whitepapers, articles and blogs explaining the Blockchain concept. I hope you will find it useful and learn a thing or two about blockchain technology</p>,<p>The article below from CoinDesk is a good guide for people who wants to know more about bitcoin and blockchain. In the end of this article CoinDesk have provided a number of very useful links for diving deeper into the crypto world.</p>,<p><a href="https://www.coindesk.com/information/what-is-blockchain-technology/" title="Click to read full article">Click to read full article..</a></p>]]></description>
            <link>http://crypto.think-like.me/beginners-guide-to-bitcoin/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">18a37c89-a473-405c-918f-7b85eb564f47</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 15:43:15 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ethereum - The machinery of change - Stork and Crow BV - Medium]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Ethereum - The machinery of change - Stork and Crow BV - Medium</h1><p>You wake up, and see that $17.27 was automatically deducted from your primary wallet, as you had authorized to happen every day, to pay the rent for your apartment.</p><img src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/2000/0*0GIMZbPL3szzmKRm.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://medium.com/@jpa_of_snc/ethereum-the-machinery-of-change-60de08222480</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">8ef0df26-fa5e-4540-af95-e2ccfeaf1d13</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2017 00:25:03 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[I Looked Into SegWit, and Here's What I Saw - Steemit]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>I Looked Into SegWit, and Here&apos;s What I Saw - Steemit</h1><p>In light of the upcoming Bitcoin fork, I finally decided to look into exactly what Segwit is, and form my opinions based on the technical and economic realities, rather than opinions and impressions I&apos;ve found online. In this post, I will share what I learned.</p><img src="https://steemitimages.com/DQmZPuWgWLogGPZNdtKsnUfdANvhACWXQeR4AswjqfrnTr6/truck.jpeg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://steemit.com/bitcoin/@modprobe/i-looked-into-segwit-and-here-s-what-i-saw</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">9979c3d1-20f7-456d-b044-94947eb52261</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2017 02:52:48 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Motherboard Bitcoin and Ethereum Primer]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><img src="https://imgflo.herokuapp.com/graph/2b2431f8e7ba7b0/696b495d9eac72b23497909b0ead6899/croprotate.jpeg?cropheight=675&cropwidth=892&degrees=0&input=https%3A%2F%2Fvideo-images.vice.com%2Farticles%2F59431309df10a05676b8f847%2Flede%2F1497612065665-shutterstock_653153323.jpeg%3Fcrop%3D1xw%3A0.8364312267657993xh%3Bcenter%2Ccenter%26resize%3D1200%3A%2A&x=149&y=0"><h1>The Motherboard Bitcoin and Ethereum Primer</h1><p>Your entry portal to the world of cryptocurrency.</p></article>,<p>2017.06.16</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://crypto.think-like.me/the-motherboard-bitcoin-and-ethereum-primer/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">bb8b5a5f-b76b-4c2b-872f-82da452babde</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2017 04:23:45 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Bitcoin's Blockchain Could Power an Alternate Internet]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>2015.01.13</p>,<article><img src="https://imgflo.herokuapp.com/graph/2b2431f8e7ba7b0/c15c5be1a052a3e98dc41505300f330f/noop.jpeg?input=https%3A%2F%2Fcdn-images-1.medium.com%2Fmax%2F1200%2F1*Ck3cQIL3-nAmpPpCdGIuBg.jpeg"><h1>How Bitcoin&apos;s Blockchain Could Power an Alternate Internet</h1><p>There&apos;s this hopelessly geeky new technology. It&apos;s too hard to understand and use. How could it ever break the mass market? Yet developers are excited, venture capital is pouring in, and industry players are taking note. Something big might be happening. That is exactly how the Web looked back in 1994&hairsp;-&hairsp;right before it exploded.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://backchannel.com/how-bitcoins-blockchain-could-power-an-alternate-internet-bb501855af67</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">48c7adf2-8266-4dac-b43e-52c5c2685c14</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 17:04:53 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Have Fun by Mining Ether with AWS Spot - James Wiggins - Medium]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Have Fun by Mining Ether with AWS Spot - James Wiggins - Medium</h1><p>A CloudFormation template that deploys an elastic Spot Fleet on AWS to mine Ether. Note: Based on some comments from this article I want to be clear: this article is not investment advice.</p><img src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1200/1*y-B9LaFU2d7L8c4qeTVDMA.png"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://medium.com/@james.s.wiggins/get-rich-quick-by-mining-ether-with-aws-spot-c7b7a3bdc149</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">beb2d426-0518-4c12-8433-72572e0497e6</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 17:36:14 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Blockchain Show]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Podcast about blockchain and crypto currencies. I find The Blockchain Show very informative as they touch on various aspects of the blockchain and crypto economy. I’ve learned about new technologies, interesting startups and new projects being build on the blockchain. I highly recommend subscribing to this podcast to get the latest news about</p>,<article><img src="https://imgflo.herokuapp.com/graph/2b2431f8e7ba7b0/9159d0c2a835f73baab89d7ccf459259/noop.jpg?input=http%3A%2F%2Fstatic.libsyn.com%2Fp%2Fassets%2F3%2F3%2F3%2F7%2F33374076d17e6977%2Fheight_250_width_250_NewTBCSlogo2017.jpg"><h1>The Blockchain Show</h1><p>The Blockchain Show with Steve Anderson, Sarah Hempfling, and Ethan Kinderknecht. The Blockchain Show is a podcast that demystifies and promotes widespread adoption of cryptocurrencies and distributed ledger technology.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://crypto.think-like.me/the-blockchain-show/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">986ad3b0-0ec1-4702-915a-a09a66cd71e3</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2017 15:08:03 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A beginner's guide to Tezos - Linda Xie - Medium]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>A beginner&apos;s guide to Tezos - Linda Xie - Medium</h1><p>According to the Tezos (&quot;Tay-zos&quot;) website, &quot;Tezos is a new decentralized blockchain that governs itself by establishing a true digital commonwealth.&quot; A commonwealth is a group that chooses to be linked together because of their shared goals and interests. Tezos aims to have their token holders make decisions together to govern the platform and improve it over time.</p><img src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1600/1*cLjDJYqI1_3cOMPmVCLIAw.png"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://medium.com/@linda.xie/a-beginners-guide-to-tezos-c9618240183f</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">a6a97eca-be97-4070-9204-1bf6627867bb</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 18:07:26 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Traders Plan for Correction as Cryptocurrency Market Tops $100 Billion - CoinDesk]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Traders Plan for Correction as Cryptocurrency Market Tops $100 Billion - CoinDesk</h1><p>The total value of all publicly traded cryptocurrencies may be at an all-time high, but trader confidence isn&apos;t keeping pace. After rising more than 1,500% from just over $7bn on 1st January, the market is beginning to show signs that its rapid ascent in 2017 may be slowing.</p><img src="https://media.coindesk.com/uploads/2017/06/shutterstock_637929982.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.coindesk.com/traders-plan-correction-cryptocurrency-market-tops-100-billion/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">78ada50e-3712-46ec-b718-76da52593479</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 15:33:56 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How to begin investing in crypto currencies:]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>How to begin investing in crypto currencies:</h1>,<p>To start investing in crypto currencies is in fact very simple. It is almost as easy as placing an order on Amazon or any other online webshop.</p>,<p>The easiest and most convenient way is creating an account on Coinbase where you can buy either Bitcoin (BTC), Ethereum (ETH) or Litecoin (LTC) directly with your credit card, or by sending money to your account via a normal bank transfer.</p>,<p>Coinbase – Coinbase lets you invest in the three most popular crypto currencies at the moment, and it is a good way for you to get your feet wet in the crypto world.</p>,<p>Use this link when you sign up to <strong>get $10 worth of BTC </strong>when you make your first purchase of any coin for at least $100: <a href="https://www.coinbase.com/join/56c1a428f892ad2729000158">https://www.coinbase.com/join/56c1a428f892ad2729000158</a></p>,<h2>Exchanges (and a vast number of different crypto currencies)</h2>,<p>If you want to invest in others of the thousands of crypto currencies available, I recommend signing up for one of the following exchanges.</p>,<p>If you want to trade other coins that are not on Coinbase you will still need to start with Coinbase. As of now that is one of the only ways to get your money into crypto currencies. In order to start buying and selling a wide variety of crypto currencies I recommend that you buy either BTC or ETH on your newly created Coinbase account. Next you will have to create an account on an exchange. Below is a little introduction to exchanges followed by a guide on how to fund your account on the exchange.</p>,<h3>Binance –</h3>,<p>Binance has become my #1 trading platform. They are fast to add new coins, they have a good trading volume, and they have been good at supporting hard forks (what not many exchanges does i.e. Coinbase &amp; Poloniex – this means that you will get free coins when a blockchain is going through a hard fork). I recommend that you create an account here as your first exchange.</p>,<p>Sign up here using my referral link: <a href="https://l.facebook.com/l.php?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.binance.com%2F%3Fref%3D11019906&amp;h=ATNTiIlQbaYyvXhscSIozye66qkA7TNf4sJvncZYL_XtGlJfwbXNs-EWPqCeAkIeSuHg8wvGM9897Ch697H_Jh3AbVSqacCmkXgh7j2XxFabXWOBXNPCZ6qo_vM3ooUyHRh76jRckF3abmgb4udTmIMJMa2CxsNZH6H6wRZGEZEkkeqsPpT6M8OFBxKWrjzD9n-6q8ZDZZJU95hiyIiTRUPbYE5h-YBP22XSqMlp5IlDf_eQFbw0Ys89wvqTrgL73QOfuEaFFS7YCflYJzjpuhHaJwmoBHaIgeijgUtAmPK9">https://www.binance.com/?ref=11019906</a></p>,<h3>Poloniex -</h3>,<p> My #2 (used to be my #1) trading platform is Poloniex. Poloniex is a well known, high volume US based exchange. They have a number of well established coins a, and a simple to use charting. If you don’t care to invest in newer coins Poloniex will be good for you. Poloniex has to my dissatisfaction NOT been supporting most of the hard forks you might have heard about in the recent weeks (afaik they only supported the Bitcoin Cash hard fork). Poloniex require you to do some verification (e.g. US citizens need to add their SSN).</p>,<p>In addition to these two exchanges there are a vast number of exchanges out there. There is no harm in signing up to multiple exchanges, so you can sign up to them all and find out, which you like the most. Here is a list of other exchanges that I use more infrequently:<br><a href="https://l.facebook.com/l.php?u=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.coinexchange.io%2F&amp;h=ATPs-maxeayyOoknMYvdRQSLbHgrX1gCHmfXA9MbO1ZpAP29gx76tus95wFJn9MwR7YX6P8PNClHwPo0L5Ba1QeB9KtssgLQvSd5jM5KnKiy1PbfHa4CRT1QwzlehC-L1YMa6jr6Yp_doELnrwU8yL0u5z6nH_mMgiocNBKAfoE68-0a8PCj-Vw6cvW1amgPNzybBGK0QXxMEpL9v_Zv4bzrUk_DV7eWa16WT4RuR4D2NNRQ3NS7X0brqnkwFAwTpfDOe5JPY-t4vmoZxdo7We63hHsLZxA-STWFthE3ekhi">www.coinexchange.io</a></p>,<p><a href="https://l.facebook.com/l.php?u=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.cryptopia.co.nz%2F&amp;h=ATMTHw4v1Ks7qm3IktQ1Erf7T8RmE6w4mfpdfaNljzzTpaIgYwGXzAvN_dvWjYvbEoz2mElaBzIKx7uQEgE69q0GR1IjGmrXemG4tbIff8lGvpfo04zMgW5NZlYk1qXDiHABP8OnGokK0KnsR56HvZKb6ltwKXgnGAF6GXT3oLVlZ2xTfdI8b0YHIURrdyHL6M4iwQ2OMzVhM_8LiWXazqJOteodzBrfB26N3eSCYepGNeCepL7nY2RX7qHUC86l4qGf_qHXQuucGgZi69AO3TLCPGuh6FKMfoPWO0sdIcMd">www.cryptopia.co.nz</a></p>,<p><a href="https://l.facebook.com/l.php?u=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.bittrex.com%2F&amp;h=ATPS5NglCoXk48EQUyeiY0YdDjvAI-PJulHVAb7XoEfwnmBFsi0j6rzmfmnwyOMnZeLIgy2h9Jttbu1ALss6zW_ui_vp1OAhmxZqpyjIpNyt-nzeAGFvw6hMyc_rWOm05ypoFAFtbn3JeVzCR0bcnfXzcwHdOh4jNGpGLqPAPzyUR4dNEzLjiRnzWIAqTZMsA021rBdBMW3DxGw2s07Edvoh-OF4hhfLEbJhdAdtti9hDsROIw6HrW5L9Je1ZWg5NgdwIViK2b0ksxFehim8jC_QCjRAtu0fiPc9D3-hqJhC">www.bittrex.com</a></p>,<p><a href="https://l.facebook.com/l.php?u=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.bitfinex.com%2F&amp;h=ATNsh_hUYfLwXfrXsW490OGzooVCWMcdYuuiAg4l1Tzdwk_0SQyk4kVjJzuerc3eXIcEOzr46fvAh0-EaF0azVkh7unrLalR7e_p0xWbYZnqZ5AuRZBa0H468gL3IjOc5VxIeejwt2dN2Zs9dG0y9O-Fj9BOGD7KtBnS5B-dZAvbBqvQHKRmoOXyc-HYIrYTd0MjuSem69Yrn_IsP173H32DK587uL3s9OXSFATCJU6Q9NzJ0p8_62aBeCen3DKgf5wKpYxX36qa3pmEHZb8c4gTrNKut1QYdSkkdwk1hJSJ">www.bitfinex.com</a> (not open US citizens anymore)</p>,<p>There are many other exchanges out there, but I have only listed the above, because these are the ones I have found to be most trustworthy and in the better end of the security-scale.</p>,<h2>Step-By-Step Guide to Transfer Your Coins to an Exchange</h2>,<p>Now that you have an account on both Coinbase and the exchange of your liking I will teach you how to start trading on the exchanges. The following example will use Binance as the example, as that is my favorite exchange, (while it might be slightly different from exchange to exchange the same logic applies to the other exchanges (PM me if you have any questions). The example will also assume that you have bought ETH on Coinbase.</p>,<p>After creating your Binance account (click <a href="https://www.binance.com/?ref=11019906" title="Create Binance Account">here </a>to create a link) you should (a) login and (b) click on Funds -&gt; Deposits Withdrawals</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/06a46808-84a8-42e4-accb-e331426149f7.png" title="Get to your Binance Wallets">,<p>You will now get to a new page showing you all your available wallets on Binance:</p>,<p>Since you are now the proud owner of ETH, you want to send some (or all) your ETH to your Binance account. You do this finding Ethereum in the list of wallets, and click on the Deposit button like this:</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/bfa01029-72d9-4961-a43f-3dc9c33472b1.png">,<p>You will now see your ETH wallet address that you need to send to from your ETH Account on Coinbase.</p>,<p>Copy the address, and go back to your Coinbase Account and select your ETH Account</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/9198abca-ff12-4a83-8487-a7304395358c.png">,<p>As seen below scroll down until you see your ETH Wallet and click on (1) Send. Now you will see a new window open up, and in the (2) Recipient (ETH Address) you paste your Binance ETH Deposit Address that you just copied from your Binance account.</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/b14ba47a-aac8-4bfe-b1f6-0811f6b68a58.png">,<p>Select the number of ETH you want to send to your Binance account, and in Note (3) I like to put a comment on each transfer I make in order to more easily remember what each transfer was for.</p>,<p><em><strong>Check, Check &amp; Double Check</strong></em> (If you send to the wrong address your coins will be lost) that you have entered the correct ETH address before you click Continue.</p>,<blockquote>Check, Check &amp; Double Check (If you send to the wrong address your coins will be lost). </blockquote>,<p>You will get a confirmation when your ETH has been sent. It can take up to several minutes before you will see your ETH on your Binance accunt, depending on how congested the network is. If you have any questions to this feel free to PM me.</p>,<p>When your ETH gets into your Binance account you are ready to invest in one of the many alt coins that Binance has listed (I will make another post regarding how you trade on Binance – until then please PM me with any questions).</p>,<p>Remember that in the crypto-world it is almost impossible to guarantee total safety of your investments, however there are different steps you can take to prevent hacks and lost coins (money). I will create a post regarding that later, and post the link here.</p>,<p>Until then please PM me for any questions.</p>,<p>Please feel free to message me directly if you have any questions regarding getting started, or you can ask questions below in the comments, and there are probably others who can help you.</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://crypto.think-like.me/how-to-get-started-with-investing-in-crypto-currencies/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">57f21587-c7cd-4d09-b370-f175f9763599</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2017 02:53:06 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>